ED.
I want to go in the pool
sea
Oh no.
Wait, it's a real pool.
Come on, look at this.
Thank you.
Beat Vance.
What? Swimming?
Oh, my God, you've got to jump in.
It's surprisingly cold.
Inokari.
I'm ready to jump in.
Don't jump in.
I didn't bring a change of pants.
I'll take off my underpants while I still can.
Succeeded in removing Inokari's pants as well and making him look lowly.
Inogari13 - I want to take them off and jump in.
Morisaki fighter
Inoue celebrates.
All right, then.
Oh, oh, oh!
Computer project
Don't stop this!
There's no one here!
Guys, come on, stop!
I'm flying!
Everybody, Ming! Ming! Ming!
Cheers
Whoa!
Oh, no!
It's gone!
It's gone for real!
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, no!
I'm so sorry!
Yes!!!
OK. It's over.
They're kind of amazing, aren't they? They. Really.
Did you jump in with gusto?
They're idiots.
There are swimmers. They're really serious.
Are you all right? Oh, no, no, no.
A lot of people who don't have anything to do with it are jumping in.
I don't like it.
Oh, no.
It's stupid. Really.
It's really stupid.
Oh, good, good, good.
Let's apologise properly.
All right, I've done it.
Let's apologise firmly.
Let's apologise.
I'm in. Her.
It was fun. You didn't want to go in.
It's true.
I should have gone in.
What do you think of this?
Oh, my God,
Oh, no,
Today is my youth.
Go ahead and float to some extent.
I'm glad I'm One Love Unheard of.
Thank you very much.
Even though I jumped in,
I'm glad I'm One Love Unheart, where I'm just about forgiven.
Not allowed.
It's unforgivable.
No, you're out, though.
Good morning!
It's sunny! And the cicadas are singing!
Oh, no! It's so hot!
Is it a good day for a photo shoot?
The lucky girls and guys are out there right now.
Really? Oh, no!
I thought there'd be some rain man or woman.
Oh, yeah! No, it's not.
When it's supposed to be sunny, it's sunny.
It's fine!
Yoo-hoo!
Last time...
It kept raining.
This time
We were able to shoot in this sunny day!
But, you know, the humidity was so high that the wood came off.
It's already straight!
I'm not going to let the humidity get the better of me!
Bye-bye!
We are
Wonderful!
Have a great day!
Please!
Start!
Staff, we'll do it once, pre-back together, and then we'll go live.
Yes! Please!
Let's all watch it together once.
Oh!
All you can see is my face!
Bye-bye.
If I laugh as hard as I can now...
I don't know if I can.
I like the way we're talking to each other.
We're really the same.
We just saw it.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have more scenes to show you.
Good job, guys.
Good work, everybody.
Good work, ladies and gentlemen.
Are you on screen?
Yes, I'm here.
We'll be filming you.
It's like we're looking back on a happy memory.
Can I get a smile?
Thank you very much for your time.
See you in the next video.
See you again.
We'll see you again.
We'll see you again
Yes, cut!
Let's see it again, shall we?
Cut.
What are you filming now?
Fireworks scene.
Yay!
We're all going to enjoy our summer youth!
Good work!
Mankind is barefoot.
I think it's important to return to our roots.
Oh, man! It really feels good.
They'll know my feet are dirty.
It's cold.
It's so cold!
Wipe.
πο Wyoming.
Wyoming
Good luck ах
Ah!
Ahh, all the way in.
Uh-oh.
Oh, there it is!
Matsumura, spinach.
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, hey!
Shime. You.
To the shining future
Wait, it's in bloom
I whispered to the reverberations
It's beautiful, isn't it?
(Pan-pan-pan-pan-pan)
(Laughs when it spins)
I can laugh as hard as I can
♪ The end ♪
♪ Dream is born in one ♪
# Beyond the bright now to the future #
♪ Beyond the bright now to the future ♪
♪ Beyond the brightest now and into the future ♪
♪ Shining beyond now and into the future... ♪
Thank you so much for being alone this morning!
Thank you very much!
Come with me!
Valen barbar!
Thank you very much!
It's over!
It's over.
Thank you very much.
Long time off music video.
To all of you who have been so kind to us.
Thank you so much!
See you in the next music video.
Good bye.